Life is a bitch
They told me that I don't know shit
Now I'm at the top of the list
Life is a bitch
I'm gonna smoke get rich
Life is a bitch huh...
Now my name on your girlfriend's lips
They told me that I don't know shit
Life is a bitch
Now I'm at the top of the list
I'm gonna smoke get rich
Life is a bitch
Now my name on your girlfriend's lips
Life is a bitch Huh
ដើរតាំងពីជើងត្រង់រហូតដល់ជើងពៀច
អត់អីសុី សុីព្រឹកខ្វះល្ងាច នៅមានច្រើនទៀត
ជីវិតដូចជាលុយ បើសិនមិនប្រថុយ
មានតែភ្លើងអត់មានឌុយ ចង់ទៅដេកមិនងងុយ
នៅតែហុយដូចសំរាម បើមិនតាមទៅមិនដល់
មើលមិនធ្លុះគិតមិនយល់
ជីវិតតាមបង្ខំអោយខ្ញុំខូច
ដើរខុសគន្លងដៀលខ្ញុំថាអាកំហូច
ពីរនាក់បងប្អូនខ្ញុំគេហៅថាអាដូច
ចរិតយើងទាំងពីរមិនដូចគេទេ
ឡើងឆាកមក Rap in the trap way fuck all the bitch
Yeah we from the bay I don't need delay
Everything ok yeah we fly today
ពាក្យថាជីវិតគឺវាចត់
វារទាមទារអោយលលាឡ៏មានអំនត់ និង អំនត់
ជីវិតបោកអ្នកប្រើអោយហត់
ស្បថនឹងខ្លួនឯង
ស្អប់នឹងខ្លួនឯង
ខឹងនឹងខ្លួនឯង
I don't know me
ទីបញ្ចប់ក៏នៅជាខ្លួនឯង ក៏នៅម្នាក់ឯង
គ្មានអ្នកណាមកជួយអ្នកឯង for free
គិតហើយនិងគិតខឹងជីវិតដែលប្រព្រឹត្តមានកូនចិត្ត និងគំនិត
But life is a bitch
មិនអាចបន្ដ ទោះខំរស់ទាំងត្រដរវានៅតែសើចចំអក
មិនកេងបន្លំមានបេះដូងដែលស្អាតស្អំនៅតែគេមើលមិនចំ
I said life is a bitch
Life is a bitch
They told me that I don't know shit
Now I'm at the top of the list
Life is a bitch
Now my name on your girlfriend's lips
Life is a bitch, but I'm a king
ដូចជាម្ចាស់, rule over my dreams
All the ស្រីស្អាត wanna fuck with me
If I could fuck one though I'd give life this D (give life this D)
Whatcha know about me
Sacrifice my needs as I build my team
But I made a life bar and a Baramey hit
Baramey skates...
Watch me make the art I made flip from the part of the States
Where the palm trees sit and the bomb weed hit
Roll a blunt right quick me and Vann Da lit
រហ័សនាម A-GVME
Y'all gonna know this name
I maintain, all up in ya Mama's mainframe
Learned how to walk again how to rock a lane
Grew from awkward game to Monsta thangs
To see the worst of people; had to walk away
All just to end up lost again
Lost in the lap of an Instagram trap, goddamn
Contoured face with a fake ass
Perform fake-ness how long can fake last
What's a legacy you can make last
I wake in the morning on missions to give
You never needed permission to live
An admission of weakness a scissor-like gift
Cut through the bull, don't end up with shit
កំពុងរវល់ ខ្ញុំរវល់ making hits
Vann Da និង A-GVME enlightenment shit
មានកំលាំងពីអ្នកតា making Baramey lit
Life is a bitch
Now I'm at the top of the list
Life is a bitch I'm gonna smoke get rich
Life is a bitch
Now my name on your girlfriend's lip